Guide to the John N. Warfield papers, 1931-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Textual Materials, 1943-2001; (51 boxes)
  - "Digital Control Theory & Stochastic Systems: Problems & Solution," University of Kansas [John N. Warfield], 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - "Digital Control Theory - EE347 Course Notes, University of Kansas [John N. Warfield], 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - "Stochastic Automata Theory - Course Notes," University of Kansas [John N. Warfield], 1964 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - "Decomposition of Sequrntoa; Machines: Bibliography," Ohio State University, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - "Overview of the Book -Introduction to Sequential Machines & Automata Theory " [John N. Warfield], 1968 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - "Untitled Paper - Test or Class Exercise based on Stochastic Theory", undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - "Digital Control Theory Notes & Related Papers," [John N. Warfield], undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - "Digital Control Theory Notes & Related Papers," [John N. Warfield], undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - "Fourier Integrals & Transforms in Communication Theory: EE409 Class Notes," [John N. Warfield], June 1965 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - "Switching Circuits as Models of Discrete Stochastic Processes," Various Articles & Notes., 1967 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - "Switching Circuits - EE660 Course Notes & Exams," Ohio State University," [John N. Warfield], 1968 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - "Syllabus for Systems Engineering Course," Case Study., January 28, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - "Electrical Communications Course EE531 Notes," University of Virginia, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - "Random Process & Applications Course in University of Virginia," Notes, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - "Communications Theory Course Notes for EE420," University of Virginia, undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - "Structural Thinking: Producing Effective Organizational," One Week Course Presented by John N. Warfield & Roxana Cardenas., June 6, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - "Demands for Complexity on Writing & Research," Short Course Given for (T.I.P.P), June 1955 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - "Complexity & Drummers," (T.I.P.P) Short Course, June 1955 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - "Complexity & Drummers," (T.I.P.P) Short Course, undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - "The Fundamentals of Symbolic Processing," [John N. Warfield], 1986 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - "Structured Programming & Interpretive Structural Modeling," [John N. Warfield], 1986 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - "Behavioral Science Relevance to Software Systems Engineering & Design," [John N. Warfield], 1986 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - "Reflections on Software Development," Draft [John N. Warfield], 1986 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - "Software Engineering Curriculum", 1984 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - "Systems Engineering for Software Productivity," [Walter R. Beam, James D. Palmer, Andrew P. Sage, March 1987 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - "Computing in Groups," High Technology Magazine Article, November 1986 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - "Programming: Sorcery or Science," IEEE Article, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - "A Software Research Institute - Proposal," George Mason University, March 1986 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - "Inner Cycle of Members in Pascal Syntax,", 1986 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - "ADA: From Promise to Practice? & Strategic Computing: A Status Report," IEEE Spectrum Magazine, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - "The Limits of Software Reliability," News Paper Article, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - "Overselling Technology: Suppose You Gave a Computer Revolution & Nobody Came?," Chronicle of Higher Education's Article, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - "Essence & Accidents of Software Engineering," Magazine Article, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - "Software Productivity Consortium - Resumes & Resume Summaries", 1985 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - "Software Productivity Research Institute Objectives," George Mason University, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - "Software Productivity Consortium: Software Cleanup ", 1986 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - "Software Productivity Research Institute: Correspondence & Proposals," George Mason University, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - "Software Productivity Research Institute: Correspondence & Proposals," George Mason University, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - "Gradual Loss of Industry, List of Handouts", 1986 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - "Department of Defense's ADA, Software for Mission Critical Systems," Article, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - "Quality Control -- A Non Topic?," Short Essay [John N. Warfield], October 1985 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - "Priorities for I.S.M. Software," [John N. Warfield], August 5, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - "A Systems Science Program at George Mason University," Planning Efforts & Correspondents, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - "A Systems Science Program at George Mason University," Planning Efforts, Miscellaneous & Correspondents., 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - "Systems Education: Resource Materials", 1982-1985 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - "Systems Education Programs & Curriculums in Other Universities", 1982-1985 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - "Washington Evolutionary Systems Society Conference", January 16, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - "Defense Systems Management College (D.S.M.C) Curriculum Plan Proposal," [John N. Warfield], 1990 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - "A Science of Generic Design: Preface," [John N. Warfield], undated (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Examples of General Systems," A List From Kenneth Boulding, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - "Global Workshop on Systems Science Education," San Jose State University, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - "Systems Directory," Compiled by Ist van Kiss, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - "City University of London: Brochures, Annual Reports & Correspondence", 1989 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - "Systems Science Program: Ohio State University," Brochures, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - "Separation Record: Grade Reports in John N. Warfield Course of Students", undated (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - "Systems Science Program: Miami University," Brochures, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - "Systems Science Program: George Mason University," Brochures, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - "Systems Science Program: S.U.N.Y Binghamton,Antioch & University of Tokyo," Brochures, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - "Software Studies Papers," [John N. Warfield], 1989 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - "Software Curriculum & Development: Correspondence", 1986 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - "Software Design & Software Test: Reference Guides", 1990 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - "ADA: Language on the Move & Why It's Not Just Another Programming Language," Articles, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - "A Model for Program Complexity," [Carma L.McClure], 1986 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - "Various Articles About Software Evaluation, Terminal Server's, Network Local Schemes", 1986 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - "ADA-Prolog: An ADA System Parallel Interpretation of Prolog Programs," [Patrick O. Bobbie], 1987 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - "Software Design Institute Advisory Committee,Working Groups," SDI Notes BM Corporation [Harlan D. Mills], 1986 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - "Laws of Programming," Communications of ACM Volume 30 [C.A.R. Hoare, I.J. Hayes, Morgan, Roscoe, Sanders, Sorenson, Spivey, Sufrin], August 1987 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Eastport Study Group: A Report to Director Strategic Defense Initiative Organization," Summer Study, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - "School Board Decisions," Science & Technology Task Force, Virginia, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - "Computers in Engineering ENGR 109: Pascal Computer Program," University of Virginia, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - "Beyond the Chalkboard: Computer Support for Collaboration & Problem Solving in Meetings," Intelligent Systems Laboratory, October 1985 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - "Reflections on Software Development," Draft [John N. Warfield], 1986 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - "The Quest for Thinking Machines: A Consortium of Rival U.S. Corporations", 1986 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - "Underconceptualization," Prepared for Presentation in Amsterdam [John N. Warfield], February 1989 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - "The Domain of Science Model: Extensions & Restrictions," [John N. Warfield], November 30, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - "Universal Priors to Science: How the Liberal Arts Could Revitalize Science," [John N. Warfield], August 1988 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - "EFL - Essay Competition," Correspondence, May 1990 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - "Design for Improving University & Industry Cooperative Research Projects," [David B. Keever], May 1987 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - "Interactive Management for Organizational Redesign," [David B. Keever, Alexander N. Christakis], 1989 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - "B-21 Files Information," Part 1, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - "B-21 Files Information," Part 2, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - "A Framebreaking & Remodeling in Organizations," Seminar [John N. Warfield], undated (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - "Foundations of Thought & Design," Seminar Talk [John N. Warfield], undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - "Design as a Group Activity," [John N. Warfield], 1989 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - "The Modern Concept for Analysis & Synthesis Based on Theory of Relations", undated (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - "Dual - Basis Design," [John N. Warfield], July 1988 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - "Forum on the Future of Pediatric Nursing: Looking Towards the 21st Century," [Irene L. Cromer, Veronica D. Feeg], May 17, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - "Technomyopia Threatens our National Security, A Critique of the Defense Science Board Software Report," [John N. Warfield], June 22, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - "Oversight & Steering for Effective System Design," [John N. Warfield], 1987 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - "Simple System Models Based on Sophisticated Assumptions," [John N. Warfield], February 12, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - "Detractors to Effective System Design," [John N. Warfield], 1987 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - "Implicit Aspects of Much Systems Thinking," [John N. Warfield], March 1988 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - "Some Thoughts on Systems Education," [John N. Warfield], 1986 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - "The Work Program of Complexity," From Origins to Outcomes [John N. Warfield], 1997 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - "Notes From Current Practices in Software Development," [David King], undated (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - "Analysis & Prescription: Software for SDI," [John N. Warfield], October 1986 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - "Software Metrics for Aiding Program Development & Debugging," N. F. Schneidewind, undated (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - "The Fifth Generation Project - A Trip Report," Reports & Articles, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - "Mathematically Provable Design, Syntax Studies, Software Productivity Consortium Project", 1985 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - "National Science Foundation Grantee Workshop on Design Theory," Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, June 5, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - "A Report on Interactive Management," George Mason University [Kenneth W. Mcllvoy], 1993 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - "Case Studies in Policy Development: Education, Government, Industry," Short Course, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - "Categorizing Complexity," Presentation at Johnson Center, George Mason University, August 1998 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - "Chronology of my Research on Complexity 1968-1998," [John N. Warfield] (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - "The Complexity Learning Sequence, Key Propositions: A User's Guide to Patterns & Behavior," [John N. Warfield], January 1988 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - "Condensed Patterns Relevant to the Science of Complexity," [John N. Warfield], 1998 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - "The Demands of Complexity Meet the Killer Assumptions: Why Policy is Defective," Short Course - PUBP740, The Institute of Public Policy, May 18, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - "Demands of Complexity Meet the Killer Assumptions - 1& 2," Presented at ICM 98 International Conference on Management, China, July 26, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - "The Work Program of Complexity: From Origins to Outcomes," Indexing Copy [John N. Warfield], 1997 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - "George Mason University Johnson Center Lecture Series on Complexity: Lecture Group 1," [John N. Warfield], 1998 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - "George Mason University Johnson Center Lecture Series on Complexity: Lecture Group 2," [John N. Warfield], 1998 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - "George Mason University Johnson Center Lecture Series on Complexity: Lecture Group 3," [John N. Warfield], 1998 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - "A Platform for Sociotechnical System Design," [John N. Warfield], 1997 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - "Problematique: Evolution of an Idea," [John N. Warfield], 1997 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - "Problematique," Correspondence with Alexander N. Christakis, 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - "A Proposal to the Institute of Public Policy: A New Track ,the Complexity Track [John N. Warfield], September 1997 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - "Readings for Bureaucrats," [John N. Warfield], April 30, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - "Missing Voices in the Social Epistemology Discussion," [John N. Warfield], May 1997 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - "Participant: Workshop on Defense Acquisition Research," Defense Systems Management College, April 1997 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - "Scientific Jeopardy," [John N. Warfield], 1997 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - "Seven Milestones in the History of Thought," Conference Paper [John N. Warfield], March 1997 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - "Strategies for Linking Producers & Users of Technology in Ghana: A Report," Council for Scientific & Industrial Research (C.S.I.R), Ghana, January 1997 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - "Twenty Laws of Complexity: Studies in the Abuse of Reason," [John N. Warfield], March 1997 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - "The Mathematics of Structure: Boolean Algebra, Sets& Binary Relations, Binary Matrices, Digraphs maps & Models," [John N. Warfield], 1997 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - "Managing Complexity," Presentation at International Systems Thinking Conference & Workshops, University of Capetown, South Africa, November 1997 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - "Interview with Dr. John Warfield,by Roxana Cardenas," [Roxana Cardenas], May 26, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - "Interpretive Structural Modeling in 1997," Lecture Presented to Picturetel," Mexico, March 13, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - "Integration Workshop on the Capacity Development & Utilization Program: A Report," Ghana, January 1997 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - "How to Design a Meeting: Context, Content, Process," [John N. Warfield], August 17, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - "Four Funerals & A Wedding or How the Grinches Stole Science," [John N. Warfield], 1997 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - "Essays on Complexity: Reviewer Copy Issued August 1997," [John N. Warfield] (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - "Essays on Complexity: A Prospects" [John N. Warfield], 1997 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - "1997 Essays on Complexity: A Midterm Edition," [John N. Warfield (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - "Essays on Complexity 1995-1996," [John N. Warfield] (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - "Essays on Complexity 1988-1994," [John N. Warfield] (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - "New Layout Techniques for Entity - Relationship Diagrams," IEEE Computer Society [Roberto Tamassia], 1985 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - "Automatic Graph Drawing & Readability of Diagrams," University of Rome [R. Tamassia, C. Batini, G. DI Battista], 1987 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Unifying the Human Sciences: A Book Proposal [Rick Szonsak], 1996 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - "System Profile: Eleven Profiles Reprinted in System Research", 1987-1994 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - "Quality Function Deployment," [L.P. Sullivan], June 1986 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - "Development of the Science Base for the Manufacturing Field Through the Axiomatic Approach," [NAM P. SUH], 1988 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - "Methods for Visual Understanding of Hierarchical System Structures," IEEE, February 1981 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - "Beyond the Chalkboard: Computer Support for Collaboration & Problem Solving in Meetings," [Mark Stefik, Greff Foster, Daniel, Kahnm Lanning Suchman], January 1987 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - "Effective Representations of Hierarchical Structures," Research ReportS [Sugiyama,Kozo, S. Tagawa], undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - "The Illusion of Perceiving Social Complexities," [R. Starkermann], undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - "Reconciling Design Theory & Methodology: QFD/TIES & It's Place in the Domain of Science Model," [Scott S. Staley, L.S. Vora], February 26, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - "Topics in Design Theory & Methodology," [Scott M. Staley], April 1991 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - "An Example IM Workshop Plan," Draft of Ford Report [Scott M. Staley, John N. Warfield], 1992 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - "Design Science as a Foundation for CAD," [Scott M. Staley], September 1991 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - "Complexity Measurement of Systems Design," [Scott M. Staley], 1995 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - "Muggers,Mugged & Affected by-Standers," Using Interactive Management as the Method [Roy Smith], November 23, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - "Book Review of the Context of Social Psychology," Science Volume 180 [J.Israel, Tajfel], 1988 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - "Study Questions on Peter Senge's Book - The Fifth Discipline," Puad 729 Course at George Mason University [John N. Warfield], 1991 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - "Software Metrics for Adding Program Development & Debugging," [N. F. Schneidewind], 1979 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - "Towards a Better Scientific Theory of Human Organizations," [Fenton F. Robb], 1985 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - "Policy Sciences: A Bibliography of Selected Rand Publications," Rand Corporation, February 1973 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - "Decision Making: A Bibliography of Selected Rand Publications," Rand Corporation, February 1973 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - "University Studies: Portland State University", undated (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - "Ghana Herbal Policy: Policy Research & Strategic Planning", 1992 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - "Challenges of Interdisciplinary Collaboration in the Social Sciences," [Craig W. Platt], October 24, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - "System Design With the Right Brain," Sixth National Congress [Frank D. Peschanel], 1984 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - "Mechanistic Misperception & Mismanagement of Complexity," [George T. Perino], September 29, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - "Complexity: A Cognitive Barrier to Defense Systems Acquisition Management," Doctoral Dissertation [George H. Perino], 1999 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - "Charles Sanders, From Reasoning & the Logic of Things," [Pierce], 1996 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Urban Management & Technological Innovations," [Vivek N. Patkar], 1990 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - "Software Aspects of Strategic Defense Systems," Communications of ACM Volume 28 [David Lorge Parnas], December 1985 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - "The Computer Delusion," Atlantic Monthly Magazine [Todd Oppenheimer], July 1997 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - "Three Page Except on Second Generation Design," Untitled Paper [Olsen], undated (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - "Structural Analysis & A Complexity Metric for High Level Software Language," Conference in Japan,Kyoto [Ohuchi, Azuma, Ikuo, Kaji, John N. Warfield, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - "Articles on I.S.M Software Programming Methods," [Ohuchi, Kurihara, Kaji], 1985 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - "Developing A Consensus Model in Flexible I.S.M," IEEE: SMC, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - "Computer-Aided Deliberation: Model Management & Group Decision Support," [J.F. Nunamaker, Lynda M. Applegate, Benn R. Konsynski], 1987 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - "Electronic Meeting Systems to Support Group Work," Communications of ACM [Unmaker], July 1991 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - "Six Articles Downloaded from Internet Site," New York Academy of Science, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - "Complexity Theory in Management: A Source of New Metaphor or Something More?," Comments on Manuscript [Peter J.Murray], 1997 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - "Towards A Better Models of the Design Process," A.I. Magazine [Jack Mostow], 1985 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - "Group Process Techniques in Public Policy Decision Making," Proceedings Twenty Sixth Annual Management Meet,Washington D.C. [Moore, John Gargan], 1982 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - "Creating Tools to Guide the Evolution of Clinical Quality in Managed Care:Product Development Missions," Proposal Molecules to Market Limited, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - "Priority Setting in Planning Rural Development Programmes," [Modal, Vivek Patkar], 1981 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - "Misconceptions & Fallacies in Software Reliability," [Harlan D. Mills], March 1986 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - "Interdisciplinary Versus Mulitdisciplinarity," Interspectives Newsletter [Miller Raymond], 1997 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - "In Order to Save the World for Human Habitation, We Must Stop Teaching Economics!," School of Education Review Volume 4[Miller Raymond], March 1993 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - "Interactive Management & The Science of Generic Design," Draft [Kenneth W. Mclivoy], September 1993 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - "A Trade-off Evaluation Procedure," U.S. Forest Service, Atlanta, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - "Mason Gazette: Mason Professor Helps Build Peace," Ben Bromme's Article, August 29, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - "Strategic Planning for Research & Management of Albacore Tuna Fishery," Options Profile Method [David Mackett], 1985 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - "Tutorial: I.S.M. for Windows 1.0," [Dangsheng Ma], 1994 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - "The New Plage: Organizations in Complexity," F.E.S Publishers,New York, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - "Problem Formulation," In Systems Engineering & Integrated Planning [Dangsheng Ma], 1987 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - "Forty Three Authors Illustrate Non-Integrative Communications Concerning the Japanese Miracle," [Michael F. Litzelman], September 28, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - "Increasing the Likelihood Value by Adding Constraints," Economics Letters Volume 28 [David Levy], 1988 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - "Making Alphabet Soup: Blending VSM,STS & TQM," [Allenna Leonard], 1992 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - "Presentation of Annual Meeting of ISGSR," Budapest,Hungary, June 5, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - "Toward a General Theory of Directed Value Accumulation & Institutional Development," [Harold D. Lasswell, Allan R. Holberg], undated (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - "Book Review: the Science of Complexity & Praxis," Journal of Communications [Krippendorff Klaus], 1986 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - "Using Decision Making Tools to Solve Quality Problems," [Steve A. Landenberg], September 24, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - "Acuity Software: Tools for Visualizing Complex Issues," Slide Presentation [Fred Langhorst], 1988 (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - "The Decision Process," College of Business & Public Administration,University of Maryland [Harold D.Lasswell], 1956 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - "The Future of Political Science," [Harold D. Lasswell], 1963 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - "Investment of Values in Development," Seminar Presentation [Harold D. Lasswell], 1973 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  - "Techniques of Decision Seminars,"Midwest Journal of Political Sciences [Harold D. Lasswell], 1960 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - "Poly Optimization Problem in Power Core Type Transformer Design," [Jerzy Kowalski], September 12, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - "Introduction to Design Methods: Basic Processual Core," Mexican Version Copy [Jerzy Kowalski], 1997 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - "The Application of Morphological Analysis to Discovering New Forms of Business," [Som D. Karamchetty], 1996 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - "Design for a Technology Assessment of Coal," [Kawamura,Boroush,Kan Chen, Alexander N. Christakis], 1979 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  - "Structuring Objectives in a Systematic Decision-Making Methodology," [Kazuhiko Kawamura, David W. Malone], 1975 (Box 37, Folder 71)
  - "Design for Improving University & Industry Cooperative Research Projects," [David B. Keever], 1985 (Box 37, Folder 72)
  - "Design of Technology Transfer Organizations for Improving Productivity in the United States," [David B. Keever], 1980 (Box 37, Folder 73)
  - "Chairing a Presidential Commission: Reflections," [John G. Kemeny], April 11, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 74)